저요, 사라에요
어떤 여자가자살하는 걸 봤어
그래, 그리고 그애생긴게 꼭 나같더라엘리자베스 차일즈?
이 여자 아파트에가보려고그래, 누군지 알아보던지
안되면 남은 물건이라도 털어와야지
계세요?
얘 말이지 은행에7만5천달러가 있어이런 제기랄
베스가 경찰이야나 경찰이라고당신 동료
그가 당신을 쫓아다녀요
이게 남자친구였다면나라도 기차 앞으로
뛰어들꺼야
무슨 일 있어?많지뭔가 바꼈는데
청문회는 어땠어?
엘리자베스 차일즈 경관,자신의 입장에서 근무 중 총격사건에대한 진술의 녹취를
시작하겠습니다..
결과적으로민간인 1명의 사상자가..뭔가 바꼈는데
키아라 때문에 왔어, 피
너 S 부인한테 하룻밤..키아라 맡기고서 열달 동안이나
나타나지 않았었거든!
우리가 뭔가, 그러니까..송별회나 뭔가 해야된다고안돼 안돼
키아라가 왔어
애가 나 죽었다고생각하면 안돼베스, 저 카티야 요
단 하나난 여럿인데가족이 없어
난 누구지??
여보세요?
베스당신 어딨었어?
어, 내가 어딨었냐고?음..
어, 얘기가 길어그래?
그래, 뭐?독일애 만났어?
그애랑은 뭐가연결되지 않아
베스?뭐야?
독일앤 죽었어죽어?
그래, 누가 쐈어내 바로 눈 앞에서!오, 세상에!
당신은 괜찮은거야?!
아니! 아니안괜찮거든!내차 뒷좌석에 있다고!
사방에 피투성이야!
젠장, 젠장할진짜네뭐가?
누가 우릴 죽이고있다는거놈들은 분명 유럽서부터
그앨 따라왔을꺼야
이런이런 망할!
뭐?아니야
아니, 아니야
그래, 그래, 그래서류가방은 받았어?
베스?뭐?
저말야?그건 나중에 걱정하자너 시체부터
처리해야돼
어떻게?나.. 나도..그.. 어떻게?
나도 몰라당신 경찰이잖아
삽 하나 사던지
확실히 할껀표본 채취해야돼어.. 표본?
머리하고 피말야베스할 수 있어
어.. 와서 좀도와주지 그래?가능하다면 그러지
이봐, 한번에하나씩 하자다시 전화할께
Orphan Black 01x02Instinct
Origianl Air Date April 6, 2013
한글자막 : Nike Plus
유감이다엘리자베스 차일즈
병신, 나쁜 자식들무능한 놈들아..
사라는 언제나우리 친구였지너 몇마디 해야지
필릭스?
흠? 음뭐라도 할 말 없어?
오, 아니, 난..못하겠어. 밥너무 정신없다
우린 짜증나는도시에서..
너의 자비, 너의 연민을애원하지거울미로에
닿지 않기를
사라를 위해사라를 위해!
사라를 위해
도대체 모르겠어
왜 걔가 자살해야해
사라 답지 않거든사라 답지 않아
그래 적어도사랑은 받았지
누구 사랑을받았는데, 너?사랑은 불완전한거야
사랑은그 자체로
불완전하거든
네가 그렇게 정의한다면뛰어내린 것도 이해되네
젠장!이봐! 워, 워
진정해!
애 놔줘, 빅!말해봐! 계속해
말해, 내 잘못이라고!
말해, 내 잘못이라고!그건.. 니..
빅! 빅!참아
다들 괴롭거든그런거야알았어
미안하다
잘못했어
안아달라는거아니거든, 빅
카티아 오브링어
베를린
넌 대체 누구니?
에, 어..몇 시에 여시죠?
저 앞하고 운전석창문이 필요해요
빅, 피곤하거든마지막 한잔만
사라를 기리는버번 이야오
오, 이런
좋잖아
됐어
이제 가기다려봐
내 차례야
세상에!
사라 딸애한테는내가 알려주고 싶어나가, 빅!
안되냐?!넌 그앨 만날 하등의
이유가 없으니까
그게 뭔데?어디 함 보자
일단은넌 약장수고내가 재정적으로
도와줄 수도 있잖아
또 사란 널 떠났어니가 괴롭혀서
도망친거잖아
그걸 바로잡고 싶은거야알았어, 가기나해
가자고필릭스
그애랑 계속닿아있고 싶어누구말야?
누구, 빅?!
그 애빅, 키아라는
사라가 아니야
사라는 죽었어돌아오지 못 한다고남자답게
받아들이라고
필릭스?
안아주라
오, 뭐야
빅!나 칼있거든
니 얼굴쑤셔버린다젠장
승천하기 전까지저기, 삼일 정도기다리는거 아니던가?
이 망한건 다 뭐야?네 추모식이지
정말 괴로웠어그래, 빅도 왔더라
넌 괴롭지 않았어?
나야 너한테 화났거든그래서 방금
니가 훔쳐온 코크로 번 돈
날려버리기로 했어
필릭스! 키아라가나 죽은 줄 알아?나도 몰라
오, 너도 모른다?빅이 S부인한테
어떻게 연락해서다 망쳐버렸거든키아라한테 얘기했는진
나도 몰라
빅그래,
너 죽고부터
더더욱 집착하고 있어키아라랑
만나고 싶어해
안돼!그래, 나도 알아!
당연히 안되지우리가 놔둘거 같에?
저기, 그거 뭐야?오른쪽 거기
그게, 내 보기엔..
피묻은거 같은데저기, 워!
무슨 일이야?
별일 아냐이것봐!별일 아냐. 별로
얘기하고 싶지 않거든
사라!
너 그 출생신고서들기억하지, 어?베스하고 또 두명?
그래, 카티야랑 엘리슨그래?
그래
머, 독일애 만났어뭐? 그애도..
또 쌍둥이야?
그래잊어버려, 필릭스
자기가 누군지 말해줬어?
아니뭐라고 하던데?!더는 안할꺼거든
나 정말..
진짜로 설명 못하겠어잘됐네, 좋아그만
저기,S부인한테 나 안죽었다고
니가 얘기좀 해줘, 알았어?
전부 다 실수였다고안돼! 절대로
니가 해
10달이나 있다가 이제서내가 나타나봐양육권 얻는게 얼마나
어려워지는지 보라고
뭐, 그래 내가 가서뭐라고 할까?
거짓말?이런 세상에
내가 아니라고 얘기해줘뭐라든 괜찮아키아라가 나
잘있다고만 알면돼
알았지?아이랑 우리 다
빠져나갈 수 있어
나한테 좋은 소식도조금 있거든사악한 쌍둥이
돈이야?
그래, 현금 7만5천달러빅 버리기엔 충분하지
그 기묘한 쌍둥이잊기에도..내 딸이랑 어디
안전한 곳을 찾는게
너무 많은걸바라는 걸까?그래, 그런가봐
뭐야?"아서 벨 형사"
뭐?!
망할새끼가 날 미행해서훔쳐간거야잘됐네
잘됐어, 그러면,우리 못 뜨는거네, 그치?안돼, 저기, 우리..
안돼, 사라!
사라! 사라!
사라! 사..
우아, 야, 안돼!그건 안돼나 작업하는거거든
매기 첸
망할 매기 첸은 또 누구야?어, 베스가 쏜 여자야
그렇지그래, 그럼 이건다
뭘까, 끝났냐?
공식 진술서라아서 벨 형사
공식 진술서
엘레자베스 차일즈 형사이건 뭐지?
이건.. 이게그 사건 같은데나 보라고 둔거네
그 애지우리가 아트한테서 돈을
되찾으려면
나 다시 베스가 돼야해오, 신이신여
니가 얼마나 경찰 장난질할 수 있을거같에?돈 찾을 때까지
아침 6시건든지금 전화 걸겠다는거야?그래, 두고봐.. 그자식
내 전화 기다리고 있을꺼야
좀 걸렸네
젠장 뭐하는 거에요?이봐, 난 명령을
따르는거 뿐이거든, 베스
저한테 도둑질 하란 명령요?부서장님이께서
"신참 손 꽉 잡고서
청문회로 곧장 들어와"라고 하셨거든
너 국경 넘기 전에확인한거야?
아트, 집이거든요!완전히 잘못 짚었어요나 잘못 짚고 그러지 않거든
그렇지?
그게..생각하시는거랑 달라요펑 가게서 정오에 봐
펑 가게?
펑 가게는 또 어디야?
폴?
너 어제밤에 어딨었어?오, 깜짝아!
그러지 마!나.. 나,어..
서에 있었지뒷배경 검토하고 있었거든
너 정직 상태잖아그래, 그래서?
청문회 재소집했잖아나 이거 꼭
해내야되는거거든
우선, 몇달만에날 거칠게 끌어앉더니만그러고는
밤 새고 밖에 있으면서
나한테 전화도 안해?또 옷입는건 갑자기
펑크족 같은건데?다시 말해봐
그게 말이지..말 마
그냥 무시할테니까너 또 중심을
잃을까봐 걱정되는거야
우리 전에도 이랬었잖아아니, 폴
우리 확실히 이런적 없었어미안, 나 해야될 일이
아주 많거든
원한다면, 나 서에 가서해도 되는데, 어때?베스, 너 준비 안됐잖아
시간이 좀 더필요하겠어나 진단해주는거야?
이런 일에 전문적으로
도움줄 사람들 잔득 있거든자기야, 제발
나한테 손대지마
그게 말야
총격때문에 너 죽겠는거나도 알거든그래도 너 몇달동안이나
나한테 말도 안했었지
폴
내가 어떻게 해야겠어?이건 내 문제야
당신이 지고갈거 아니거든내가, 할거지
매일 밤 잠 못들고깨어있을 수도 없고네가 숨쉬는지 확인할 수도,
니가 약에, 술에,
신만 아시는 뭐 그런 것들섞어 먹는지 걱정할 수도 없어..그러니 한동안 코디네
돌아가 있을레
알았어
그래, 너가 그렇다면야
"펑크족" 같다고?
안녕, 귀염둥이우리 엄마 봤어요?
어음.. 얘 그게..
오-오, S 아줌마윗층에 가있어라
키아라, 아가야
필릭스 삼촌이 해명해야될게 좀 있거든
사실이라고 하기엔너무 좋다 싶더라사라가 자살하기엔
너무 강한 구석이 있지
내가 맡아온 떠돌이 강아지중에 최고지
으쓱거리지 마라장례식 꾸민건
빅 을 떼놓으려던 거네
넌 어쩌다 그런 멍청한계획을 돕게 된거냐?빅 이 등신이잖아요
괴롭지그런 여자애들은시작부터가 그래
그건 또 무슨 말씀이세요?걔한테 말해
걔가 자기 딸 거의일년동안이나 보러 안왔고그리고, 그렇게 있을꺼면
난 그게 제일 나을꺼 같다
직접 말씀하시는건 어때요쇼반?전 중간에서 필릭스 짓
안할꺼에요
오, 그래? 너 걔가 까딱하고불러서 온거잖아, 아니야?
예, 그래요! 전 키아라가자기 엄마가 죽었다고 생각 않기를
확실히 하러 온거거든요그래서, 어, 좋네요, 보니까..
아니네요
아줌마랑 사라, 아줌마가남은걸 처리하실 수 있잖아요내 인생의 몇 년
내 모든 사람들을 두고런던을 떠나면서너희 둘을 새출발 시키려고
여기로 데려왔다
모든 걸 다 다시 하겠지필릭스
망할놈의 경찰들이찾아올 때마다실종자 보고가
있을 때마다
우리가 주먹을날릴 때마다왜냐면 키아라는
축복이거든
사라도 알아요아니, 걘 전혀 몰라
걔도 노력하고 있어요절실히요, 장담해요
자기 멋대로긴 해도, 걔도,진짜 열심히 한다고요
또 보네와봐
와봐, 귀염둥아
엄마는 언제와요?
언젠 줄 알잖니, 얘야준비가 되거든요?
그리고?엄마가 준비됐다고
아줌마가 말해줄때요?
그게 맞는 얘기지
바로 여기가내가 입 을 봤다고
여겼던 곳이네
그때 내 무기를 꺼내 들었고
그녀는..그녀가 어떻했더라?
그거 뇌물 아니거든요아트, 아니라고요
그럼 헛소린 집어치고, 베스어디서 난건지나 얘기해봐
폴꺼에요, 됐어요?폴하고 제꺼요
우리 공동 은행 계좌를정리한거라고요아직 그이한테는 말 안했는데
예, 동네를 뜨려고하긴 했는데못하겠더라고요, 됐어요?
돌아왔다고요
폴 때문에..총격사건 정리하러요, 아트
전 썩은게 아니라그냥 정신이 나간거였다고요
너 도청장치 했냐?아뇨!
너 이전에 절대피해자 본적 없는거지?마가렛 첸하고 전에
접촉이 없었지?
예!만약에 여기에
다른 이야기가 더 있다거나
그 돈이 어떻게든연결이 되있거든얘기는 딱 한가지에요
아트
그럼 다시 한번 나한테보여줘봐
그래야 니가 심문에무너지지 않을꺼라는거라 믿지전 저 혼자였고
다른 사건에 증인들을탐문하고 있었죠무슨 사건?
램지 껀썬 보석상 강도사건램지 껀이요
썬 보석상 강도사건이죠전 입 을 찾고있지도
않았는데
입 누구?젱 입, 미연방 공갈범으로
영장이 나왔죠
그날 아침에 기록을 봤어요..아시아계 여성, 41세그래서?
그래서..
바로 여기가..제가 입 을 봤다고
여겼던 곳이죠
여겼다고?그래요
그 여잘 봤다고요
전 그녀 이름을 불렀고멈추라고 말했어요그여잔 불응했고
도망쳤어
사라져 버렸죠..선배 저 긴장하게 만들거든요
잘됐네이제, 너도
어떤 느낌인지 알겠지
언제 무기를 꺼내들었지?제가 뒷마당에 들어섰을때
꺼냈어요, 여기요
그때 제 무기를 꺼내들었죠그리고는 그녀가 이쪽으로
사라졌고
전 바로 건너갔죠그리고 그때 뒤에서
인기척이 들렸고요
전 뒤돌아서서..빵!
발포했죠
두발이요
둘다 검정옷을 입었었죠그녀가 아니였어
그녀가 아니였어요그리고는?
그리고는 그여자 손에전화기를 봤고
전 신고를 했죠그때 선배가 나타났죠
사람들이 니가신고하기 전에
나한테 전화한걸 알게되면베스깊이 파보기 시작할꺼야
파보기 시작하면약을 찾아 낼거고또, 약을 찾게 되면은
넌 심문에 못견뎌 무너지고니 알랑거리는 엉덩일
감싸주느라 내가
피해자 손에 핸드폰을쥐어준걸 떠들어대겠지
그럴리가요, 아트제가 한 일은
제가 지고가야죠
매기 첸은 그저때와 장소가
맞지 않았던 거에요
그런거죠
선배한테까지 않갈꺼에요좋아
그래도, 확실히 해야지너 깨끗이 처리될 때까지
그 돈은
내가 가지고 있겠어그건 어때?
키아란 괜찮아
니 딸한테너 죽은거 아니야
이리와
알아, 알아
내가 돌아온거 알지아니야?
그애가 느껴져
걔도 알아너에 대해 물었어
걔도 안다고그렇지알았어
S 부인은 어때?
그 걱정은 지금 마알았지?나중에 할 수 있어
고마워
다만 너 또 떠날 때우리도 같이 데려가약속할께, 약속해
약속해
그래 됐어너 차 한잔 할래?그래
그래서 내가 베스 총격에서깨끗해질 때까진
아트가 돈을 안줄꺼야그말은 저기,
경찰 위원회 앞에서
그뭐, 변호사들이랑,교차진술 그런거 하러
돌아간다는 거야?그래
내 걱정거리 중에제일 쉬운거야
그거 베스꺼 다른 폰이네
그 독일애야?분명히 독일앤 아니야
됐다. 지금이 너 나한테실제로 무슨 일이 돌아가는지
얘기해 줄 땐거 같다
베스는 자기 쌍둥이들도조사하고 있었어내가 보기엔 그애가 찾은게
뭐든지 갤 미치게 만들었고
스스로 끝내버린거야뭐야?
그래 받아야 될까?안돼!안돼!
혼자선 어떻게 못하겠어그럼 뭐하러 물어본건데?
여보세요, 어, 저..음, 저 베슨데요
드디어!그동안 어딨었어?바빴어, 정말로
그래. 독일애서류가방은 챙긴거야?아니, 왜?
그야 너보고 하랬잖아걔 어디 머무는데, 베스?
여보세요
잠깐만!
보자
어,칼스브로 호텔, 303호
그럼, 가봐놈들이 찾기 전에
서류가방 챙겨
밤 12시에 다시 전화할께가방에..
가방에 뭐가 들었는데?저건 누구야?
내가 뭐 좀알꺼같을 때마다잘못 안거네
워, 잠깐만
베스카티야
앨리슨 헨드릭스얘가 걜까?
나도 몰라, 필릭스그럼, 독일애는
어떻게 됐어?
너 진짜로 거기 가려고?넌 그 서류가방에 뭐가 들었는지
궁금하지 않아?
않거든!현금?
아직도 난장판이네, 피이거 빌려가도 되지?
안돼, 그래모르겠다
Guten morgen(독일어 굿모닝)카티야 오브링어
사라걱정마
너 진짜 섹시해 보인다좋잖아, 않그래?
Nein, nein(독일어 No, No)
오블링어 양
오블링어 양?오블링어 양!
오블링어 양!
저 여자 맞아?예
젠장
제기랄
에헴 예안녕하세요, 에이버립니다
안내데스크에서 왔는데요
저희가 아래층에서 손님께말씀드릴게 있습니다
내방엔 왜 들어가려고했는데요?소음에 대한
불만이 있었습니다
그에 따라 보안 확인이필요했죠아가씨,
방이 지저분하더군요
록앤롤"록앤롤"이요?
싱크대가 부셔졌는데요?도대체 뭐가 어떻게
되신거 아닌가요?
안타깝지만, 항목별 청구서를뽑았습니다싱크대, 거울
베개 세개6천 달러?
6,437.11이죠, 예예
그래? 제 카드 기록가지고 계시죠, 예?
예
거기에 제 서류가방요
기다려 주시죠
승인 중입니다
파티가 정말끝내줬나보군요
전부 순서대로나와있습니다이렇게 되서 죄송합니다
에헴!시내는 즐거우신가요?
죽여주는군요Danke schoen
(독일어 Thank you)
다니엘 포니에
카티야
호주 애
이태리 애?
다니엘 포니에, 프랑스
앨리슨 헨드릭스
스카브로우
실제 동네 친구네
칼이네
여보세요?저기, 호텔에는 가봤어?
그래, 근데 누가 먼저다녀갔더라놈들이 방을 뒤졌더라고
젠장!서류가방은 없고?그렇단 말은 안했어
찾은거야, 아니야?
잠깐만
엿먹으라지
여보세요?넌 도대체 누구야?베스?
앨리슨?넌 누구야?
너 누구냐고?!베스는 빠졌어
너 앨리슨이야?
단 하나난 여럿가족도 없어
난 누구지?
그래, 미안, 수수께끼는나한테 의미 없거든이봐, 베스는 나보고
서류가방 가지고 있으랬어
너한테 가져다주길 바래?
"35 블랙오크 거리"
그만해!너가 그만해!
너가 그만해!얘들아 얘들아!
안돼 안돼 안돼
괴롭히면 안되지이런 제기랄
학부형 아줌마네
동생 따라가뛰지 말고
잘한다!잘한다
거기 너 출발
저쪽이야!
여보세요?
뛰어, 뛰어!
비비안! 내가 이거깍아올께.. 그래
대답 좀들으려는거 뿐이거든너 정신 나간거야?
어떻게 감히 애들 있는데얼굴을 드러내다니
난 어떻게 찾았어?독일애한테
주소가 있었어
네가 원하는건나한테 있지서류가방 가지고 있다고
멍청아, 지금 누구한테얘기하는지 알기나 알아?
베스는 어딨어?
어, 죽었는데
뭐?유감이야
그애 자살했어
아냐, 아냐, 아냐걔가 그럴리 없어불가능 하다고
아니, 유감이지만내가 직접 봤거든아냐, 그럴리가
이봐, 설명해줄께, 괜찮지?내 이름은 사라야..
니가 누군진 상관 없거든왜요, 하나님?
왜 제가?
이런 데 끼고싶은 맘눈꼽만치도 없었는데내 등에 "차버려"라고
크게 써있나?제발, 말 좀 해봐..
우린 서로한테 뭐지?너 지금 장난해?
난 장난 아니거든아니지, 그건
내 책임이 아니야..
있잖아너 여기서 나가야겠어가서 전화 기다려
에, 이 망할게 뭔지..가라고!
나한테 손대지마
내 이웃들 있꺼든가서 전화 기다려
아, 그리고 나가면서
니 못난 얼굴 가리고
망할 년좋아, 오렌지다, 얘들아!
두개 먹어도 되요?
그래, 넌 두개
뭐에요, 아트?너 어딨어?
집이요. 버번 마시면서욕탕에 있어요문 두드리는거 안들려?
아니지?그야 너 집에 없으니까
그게, 저 스카보로에 있어요뭐야? 왜?!
베드배스 앤 비욘드(가정용품체인점)에들리려고요, 됐어요?그런건 알리고
싶지도 않고
이봐, 뭐가됐든, 베스너 망할 상담의한테
뭐라고 짓거린거야?
그여자가 너 근무에맞지 않다고 결정했어뭐? 왜요?
그래서, 맞지 않는단 말은내일 청문회 없다는 거고오, 젠장!
그말은 이 망할게계속 계속 지속되면..끝날때까진 네 돈은
내가 보관한다는 거다
지금 가서 그여자 만나보죠안되지 안돼, 그러기엔
너무 늦었고, 베스
한번 더 약속 잡죠, 예?그여자한테 긴급사항이다
걱정 안해도 된다고 할께요
그여자 제 담당의잖아요절 만나줘야만 하죠그래서, 뭐라고 말하면
그여자 생각이 바뀔거 같은데?
뭔가 생각이 나겠죠미안하지만요
제 의견으론 형사님은아직 근무하실 준비가 안됐습니다제가, 지금..
나아지고 있어요한창 나아지고 있죠말해봐요
있잖아요, 그런 죄책감..휴대폰 보고서
"총"으로 응수한거요
지난번에 저희가 봤을 때랑똑같은 말씀만 하시는군요아뇨, 전 제 실수를
인정한다고요
바워즈 박사님말씀하신대로,
사실을 받아들이고 있어요
솔직히, 지금 저에게가장 필요한 건
근무에 복귀하는거에요
지난번 뵀을때형사님은 총쏜걸
기억하지 못하셨죠"제 자신을 놓치고 있어요깜빡거리고
고장났던지, 그래요"기억해요
괜찮습니다
제가 하려는건앞으로 나아가는거에요죄송해요, 베스. 그래도
당신의 정신 상태를 고려하고그 사건에 대해 되집어보고..그건 이제 지난 일이에요
바워즈 박사님
또한 당신 자신이 인정한기억 상실이나 정신적 문제로 인하여근무를 권해드리지 못하겠네요
저한테는 도움이되지 않을겁니다
이해해요당신은 경찰이시니하지만 이게 제 일이에요
그 뒤에꺼 다시 읽어주시겠어요?
그거, 음.."제 자신을 놓치고 있어요
깜빡거리고"
취한 것처럼 들리지 않으세요?
"깜빡거린"다는게 취한거라고요?맹맹하고, 덜깨고, 늘어지고
에헴!알레비아,슈퍼프렉스, 드락스필
기분 조절제하고항정신성 약하고차이점이 뭐죠, 다시 좀요?
베스..아, 아니다, 죄송해요
제가 좀 헷갈려서요
제 말은, 아주 헷갈리네요
항우울제, 항불안제SSRI(항우울제 종류)세로트로낙스..
이건 자극제네요
우리가 서로 한동안알고 지냈었는데 지금, 베스..그래요? 거기서 부터
잘못 알고 계시는군요
당신이 계속해서개인적으로 처방전을
애원하면서절 시험하셨잖아요
알아요제 잘못이죠
그래서 위원회에 가서당신이 이중삼중으로
처방해준 약들을 먹고
그 불쌍한 민간인을 쐈다고얘기하려고요
아니면 제가 좀 나아졌나요?
좋습니다,모두들 오셨으면다시 한번 진행해보도록
하겠습니다
이 위원회는올해 10월 7일 있었던근무중 총격 사망 사건으로
소집되었습니다
기록을 위해 당신의이름과 계급을 진술해주시고시작하세요
엘리자베스 차일즈 형사입니다
잘 하셨어요
이틀 있다가처분이 결정될겁니다
알았어요
사라에요그래, 사라
빨리 말할께
좋아넌 이미 내가
어디사는지 알테고
내가 애 봐줄 사람을못찾아서오늘밤 9시 지나서
잠깐 들려
지금 당장은 안돼?오늘밤! 독일애한테
얻은거 가져오고
뒤로 돌아서지하실 문으로 와서조용히 두들겨!
나쁘진 않았네, 차일즈
나쁘지 않았어
확실히 했다고요, 선배세세한거 까지도요
그래, 그래도아직 결정은 안났어신난거 다 티나거든요
나야 언제나 신나잖아뭐에요, 아트
이제 저 좀좋아해주셔도 되잖아요?왜 그렇게 깐깐하게
구시는거에요?
왜냐면니가 날 좋아하는
부분이 그런거잖아
저기, 폴은 제가
우리 계좌에서 돈 뺀거모르거든요그이가 알아차리기 전에
돌려놓고 싶은데요, 예?너가 복귀될때까지는
내가 맡고 있을꺼야
그렇게 하기로 했고그렇게 하기로 한건 아니고
그냥 선배가 얘기한거지..
널 보호하려는 거다파트너
오, 이런 세상에!우!
우리가 교외로 나간다고얘기했으면나 절대로 안따라올꺼
알고 있었지?
우이, 뭐하는 거야?멈추지마
누가 말걸지도 몰라
이런!세상에
나 시내에서 나오기만 하면피부가 일어나는거 알잖아
그치, 그치바로 여기
봐바.. 뾰루지
아니뾰루지 안보이는데
내 얼굴 빨게?여기 빨갛잖아!
바로 여기!
쬐만하고, 작은 교외스트레스 여드름이야안좋은 집들에
직접 가까이 가서 그래
이봐, 피이틀있으면
나 그 돈 갖게돼
알았어? 그리고 그땐..이봐S 부인과는
내가 잘 해결할께
그리고 우리 키아라 데리고어디 조용한데 가자, 어?어디 따뜻한데
그래, 부탁이야그래 저 집엔
뭐가 있는데?
오래 안걸릴꺼야오, 세상에!
안에 누가 있냐고?
여기있어, 알았지?독일애야?
독일애는 죽었어
죽었다고?!죽었다고?!안됐지, 그래
이번엔 초조해하는학부형 아줌마야
헤이, 사라! 너 맨날나한테 이러더라!니가 내 뒤 좀 봐줬으면
좋겠거든, 알았지?
나 뒤 안봐줄레!뒤 봐준다는게
뭔지도 모르겠다!
30분만 기다려나보고 그 때까지
뭐하고 있으라고?
그냥 있어누군가는 내가 어딨는지
알고 있어야되거든
잠깐, 그거 위로가안되거든! 사라!사..!
문 닫고, 잠궈
진짜로?
조용히해.애들 자고 있어애들 자고 있는데
날 쏘겠다는 거야?너 때문에 깨거나 네 얼굴을
보인다면, 그래 쏴버리지
그게 난 혈연관계는모르고 지냈는데너랑 쌍둥이 되는거
진짜 거지같다
너 진짜 아무것도모르는구나, 그치?
안녕난 코시마야
빌어먹을우리 전화로 얘기했었지
우리가 몇이나 있는거야?
우린 복제인간이야누군가의 실험물이고놈들은 우릴 죽이고 있어!
이런게 도움이 돼?오, 놀래라!
우리 마당에서 뭐하는거에요?
넌 답을 원하고난 서류가방을 원해정말로, 사느냐 죽느냐야
내가 내 딸을 뺐어와야되면나란 엄마는 도대체 뭐가돼?
자네 복귀됐네이런, 젠장!
그래, 나 빌어먹을사건 현장에서빌어먹을 경찰 흉내내거든
그러니 저 빌어먹을 지문에빌어먹을 자료가 나오는지
봐야겠어
꼼짝마! 경찰이다!
베스!
Hey, it's Sarah.
I saw a girl kill herself.
Ew!
Yeah, and she lookedexactly like me.
Elizabeth Childs?
I'm going to go up to her flat.
To find out who she is or torob the rest of her shit?
Hello?
She's got $75,000in a savings account.
Holy shite.
Beth is a cop.I'm a cop.
Your partner,he was following you.
If that was my boyfriend,
I'd jump in frontof a train, too.
- What's happened?- A lot.
Something's different.How was the hearing?
Officer Elizabeth Childs,entering into record
her version of theline-of-duty shooting...
resulting ina civilian fatality...
Something's different.
I'm here for Kira, Fe.
You left Kira with Mrs. S...
and you didn't comeback for 10 months!
We have to have, like,a memorial sendoff.
No no no,Kira's there.
She can't think I'm dead, Fe.
Beth, it's Katja.
Just one.I'm a few.
No family, too.Who am I?
Hello?
Beth,where have you been?
Uh, where have I been?
Um...
Uh, long story.
Well?
Well, what?
Did you meet the German?
I can't get a hold of her.
Beth?
What?
The German's dead.
Dead?
Yeah, someone shot her,right in front of me!
Oh, Jesus!Are you all right?!
No! No, I'm notall right!
She's in the back of my car!
There's blood everywhere!
Holy shit. Holyshit, it's true.
What?
That someone is killing us.
They must've followedher from Europe.
Jesus
bloody Christ!
What?
Nothing.Nothing, nothing.
Okay, okay, okay. Didyou get the briefcase?
Uh...
Beth?
What?
You know what?Worry about that later.
You need to get ridof the body.
- How?- I... I...
Like, how?
I don't know.
You're the cop.Like, buy a shovel.
Just make sureyou get her samples.
Uh... samples?
Hair and blood, Beth.
You can do this.
Uh... how aboutyou come help me?
I would if I could.
Look, one step at a time.
I'll call you back.
Orphan Black 01x02Instinct
Origianl Air Date April 6, 2013
Sorry, Elizabeth Childs.
Freaks and punks,
lost puppies...
We always hada friend in Sarah.
You have a few words, Felix?
Hmm? Mm.
Anything you want to express?
Oh, no, I...I can't, Bob.
I'm too verklempt.
"We're inbummed-out city...
I plead your mercyand your pity
is not life
a mirror maze?"
To Sarah.
To Sarah!
I can't figure out
why she killed herself.
It's just not Sarah.
It's not Sarah.
Well, at least she had love.
Whose love did she have, yours?
Love  is imperfect.
Love is
imperfection itself.
If that's your definition,
no wonder she jumped.
Shit!
Hey! Whoa whoa, take it easy!
Let him go, Vic!
Say it! Go ahead,say it's my fault!
Say it's my fault!
It's... your...
Vic! Vic!Be cool.
Aaah!
Everyone's raw.It's okay.
All right.I'm sorry.
My bad.
I'm not a huggy griever, Vic.
Katja Obinger.
Berlin.
Who the hell are you?
Eh. Oh, what timedo you open?
I need a front anddriver's-side window.
Vic, I'm tired.
One last drink.
A bourbon for Sarah.
Oh.Oh, Jesus.
Very good.
Okay.
Off you go.
Wait a minute.My turn.
God!
I want to get to knowSarah's daughter.
Out, Vic!
Why not?!
There's a reasonyou never met her.
What is it?
Well, let's see.
For starters,you're a drug dealer.
I could help her financially.
And Sarah left you.
She ran because you're abusive.
I want to make up for that.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
Felix,
I want to stayconnected to her.
To who?Who, Vic?!
Her.
Vic, Kira is not Sarah.
Sarah's dead and she'snot coming back.
You need to man upand accept that.
Felix?
Hug me.
Oh, come on.
Vic!I have a knife
and I will stab youin the face!
Shit.
Aren't you supposedto wait, like,
three days before rising?
What the hell's this?
That is your wake.
It was agony.
Yeah, Vic was here.Why'd you have one?
Because I was mad at you,
so I just decidedto blow all the money
from your stolen coke on it.
Felix! Does Kirathink I'm dead?
I don't know.
Oh, you don't know?
Vic screwed everything up
when he got holdof Mrs. S., somehow.
I don't knowwhat she told Kira.
Vic.
Yeah.Since you died,
he's even more obsessed.
He wants to meet Kira.
No!
No, I know that!
Of course not. You thinkwe'd let that happen?
Hey, what's that?
Right there.Well, it looks like...
It looks like blood.
Hey, whoa!What's going on?
- Nothing.- Hey!
Nothing. I don't wantto talk about it.
Sarah!
You remember thosebirth certificates, yeah?
Beth's and the two others?
Yeah, Katja and Alison.
- Yeah?- Yeah.
Well, I met the German.
What? Is she...another twin?
Yeah.
- Leave it out, Felix.- Did she say who she was?
- Don't.- What did she say?!
I'm not gettinginto it. I can't...
- I seriously cannot explain it.- All right, fine.
Stop.
Look,
I need you to tell Mrs. S.I'm not dead, yeah?
That it was all a mistake.
No! No way.You do it.
If I walk in there now,after 10 months,
think about how hardshe can make custody.
What, so I go inand I say what?
Lie?
My God.
Tell her it wasn't me.I don't care.
Just make sure Kiraknows that I'm fine.
Yeah?
We can still get out with her.
That's my one bit of good news.
Is this evil twin's money?
Yeah, $75,000 in cash.
That's enough to lose Vic,
lose the twin-sister weirdness,
just somewhere safewith my daughter.
Is that so much to ask?
Yeah, maybe.
What?
"Detective Arthur Bell".
What?!
Bastard must've followedme and nicked it.
All right.
All right, let's notgo off, though, okay?
No. Hey, let's...No, Sarah!
Agh!
Sarah! Sarah!
Aah!
Bastard!
Sarah! S...
Whoa, hey, no!Not that.
I'm working on that.
Maggie Chen.
Who the hell is Maggie Chen?
Uh, it's the woman Beth shot.
Right.
So, now, what arethese, all right?
Official statement.
Detective Arthur Bell,official statement.
Detective Elizabeth Childs.
What is this?
This is... this is,like, the case.
He left it for me.
Her.
If we want the moneyback from Art,
I to have to be Beth again.
Oh, for Christ's sake.
How long can you keepgaming a cop?
'Til I get our money.
It's 6:00 in the morning.You're going to call him now?
Yeah, believe me... thiscall, he's waiting for.
Took you a while.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, I'm just followingorders, Beth.
Orders to steal from me?
The lieutenant said "Takeyour rookie by the hand,
walk her right throughthe hearing."
Did you stop to check it beforeyou crossed the border?
Art, I'm at home!You got it all wrong.
I never get it all wrong, do I?
Well, it's not what you think.
Meet me at Fung's at noon.
Fung's?
What the hell's Fung's?
Paul?
Where were you last night?
Aw, shit!
Don't do that!
I... I, uh...
I was at the station,
I was catching upon this backlog.
You're under suspension.
Yeah, so?
They reconvened the hearing.
I have to get on topof this stuff.
First, you screw me wildfor the first time
in months, and then,you don't even call me
to tell me that you'reout all night?
And why are yousuddenly dressing
like a punk-rock ho?
Say again.
No.
You know what?Don't.
I'm going to ignore that.
I'm worried you'relosing the plot again.
We've been here before.
No, Paul,
we definitely haven'tbeen here before.
Sorry. I've gota lot of work to do.
If you want, I can take itto the station, yeah?
Beth, you're notready for this.
You need to take more time.
Is that a diagnosis?Because I have plenty
of professional help for that.
- Babe, please...- Don't touch me.
You know,
I can see this shootingis killing you,
but you stopped talkingto me months ago.
Paul.
What am I supposed to do?
It's my problem.
You don't have to take this on.
Well, I have.
And I can't keepwaking up every night,
checking your breathing,worried you're mixing
your meds, booze, Godknows what else, so...
I'm going back to Cody'sfor a while.
Okay.
Yeah, if that's what you want.
"Punk-rock ho"?
Oh.
Hi, monkey.
Did you see my mum?
Oh.Um, sweetie...
Oi-oi, Mrs. S.
Go onupstairs, Kira, love.
Uncle Felix has gotsome explaining to do.
I knew it wastoo good to be true.
Sarah's too toughto commit suicide.
Most feral muttI ever took in.
Don't shrug.
Staging a funeralto get away from Vic.
Why would you help withsuch a stupid plan?
Vic's a dick.
Plagued, that girl was,
from the very start.
What do you mean by that?
Tell her
that she hasn't seen herdaughter in almost a year
and I think it's bestif it stays like that.
Why don't you tell heryourself, Siobhan?
I'm not going to playFelix in the middle.
Oh, no? You're here at herbeck and call, aren't you?
Yes, I am! To make surethat Kira doesn't think
that her mother's dead.
And, oh, good, look...she doesn't.
You and Sarah, youcan work out the rest.
Years of my life.
Leaving London,all my people there,
to bring the two of youhere for a fresh start.
I'd do it all again, Felix.
Every visit fromthe bloody police,
every missing-persons report,
every punch we threw,
because Kira is a gift.
Sarah knows that.
No, she hasn't a clue.
She is trying.
Badly, granted,
but in her own way, she is,she's really trying
Ohh.
Caught ya.
C'mere.C'mere, monkey.
When is mummy coming?
You know when, love.
When she's ready?
And?
When you say she's ready?
Sounds fair to me.
Right here
is where I thought I saw Yip.
That's when I drew my weapon.
She...
What'd she do?
It's not a payoff,Art, it's not.
Then cut the shit, Beth,
and tell me where it came from.
It's Paul's, okay?
It's Paul's and mine.
I cleaned out our jointsavings account.
I haven't told him yet.
Yeah, I was going toleave town,
but I couldn't do it,okay? I turned around.
For Paul.
To clear the shooting, Art.
I'm not dirty,I just freaked out.
Are you wearing a wire?
No!
You never saw the vic before?
No previous contactwith Margaret Chen?
No!
If there is anotherversion of the story,
if that moneyis somehow connected.
There's only one story, Art.
Then walk me through it again,
so I know you won'tcrack under questioning.
I was by myself, I was
canvassing witnesseson another case.
Which case?
The Ramsay thing.Sun Jewelry heist.
The Ramsay thing.
Sun Jewelry heist.
I wasn't even looking for Yip.
Yip who?
Xan Yip, U.S. racketeeringwarrant. I'd seen
her sheet that morning...Asian female, 41.
And?
And...
Right here...
Is where I thought I saw Yip.
You thought?
I did.I saw her.
I called her name,I told her to freeze.
She didn't.She ran.
Disappeared down...
You're making me nervous.
Good.
Now, you know how it feels.
When did you draw your weapon?
I drew when I enteredthe courtyard, here.
That's when I drew my weapon.
And then she disappeareddown there.
I crossed to there.
And that's when I heardsomebody behind me
and I turned around...
Poogh!And I fired
twice.
They were both wearing black.
It wasn't her.
Then what?
Then I saw the phonein her hand
and I called it in.
And then you showed up.
If they find outyou called me
before you called it in,Beth,
they're going to start to dig.
And if they dig,they find the pills
and, if they find the pills,
you may crack under questioning
and tell themthat I put the phone
in the vic's hand tocover your tweaker ass.
I wouldn't do that, Art.
I got to carry what I did.
Maggie Chen was
in the wrong placeat the wrong time.
That's it.
None of this ends up on you.
Good.
But, to be sure,
I'm going to hang onto that money
until you're cleared.
How's that?
Kira's fine.
You're not deadto your daughter.
C'mere.
I know. I know.
She knows I'm back,doesn't she?
I can feel her.
She knows. She's beenasking for you.
She knows.I know.
Okay.What about Mrs. S.?
Don't worry aboutthat now, okay?
We'll work it out later.
Thank you.
Just take us with youwhen you leave again.
I promise, I promise,I promise.
All right.Do you want a cuppa?
Yeah.
So Art won'tgive me the money
until I clear Beth's shooting.
What do you mean,like, go back
in front of a police board,
with, like, lawyersand cross-examination,
- and stuff?- Yeah.
That's the least of my worries.
That's Beth's other phone.
Is that the German?
It's definitely not the German.
All right, I think it's time
that you told me what'sactually going on.
Beth was investigatingher twins, too.
I think whatever shefound out drove her nuts
and she topped herself.
What?
So do I pick up?No!
No!
I can't help myself.
Then why even ask?
Shh.
Hello, uh, this is,um, this is Beth.
Finally!Where have you been?
Busy, obviously.
Right. Did you getthe German's briefcase?
No. Why?
Because I told you to.
Where is she staying, Beth?
Hello.
One sec!
Okay.
Uh,
Carlsborough Hotel, room 303.
Well, go,
get the briefcasebefore they do.
I'll call backat midnight.
What's in...
What's in the briefcase?
Who is that?
Every time I thinkI know something,
I'm wrong.
Whoa, hold on.
Beth,
Katja,
and Alison Hendrix.
Is it her?
I don't know, Felix.
Well, what happenedto the German?
Are you seriously going there?
Don't you want to knowwhat's in the briefcase?
No!
Cash?
It's still a hustle, Fe.
Can I borrow this?
No. Yeah.I don't know.
Mmm.
Guten morgen.
Katja Obinger.
Sarah.
Don't worry.
You actually lookkind of hot.
It's good, innit?
Nein, nein.
Miss Obinger.
Miss Obinger?
Miss Obinger!
- Was that her?- Yeah.
♪ Yeah
Shit.
Ahem. Ja.
Hello. Avery,from the front desk.
Could we talk with youdownstairs, please?
Why would you go in my room?
We had a noise complaint,
which led to a security check.
Ma'am, your room was trashed.
Rock-n-roll.
"Rock-n-roll"?
The sink is broken.
What the heckis wrong with you?
Unfortunately, we havean itemized bill.
Sink, mirror,
three pillows.
$6,000?
$6,437.11, yes.
Ja.
So? You have my cardon file, ja?
Yes.
And my briefcase.
One moment.
Authorizing.
Must've been a heck of a party.
Everything appearsto be in order.
I'm very sorry about this.
Ahem!
Are you enjoying the city?
It's killing me.
Danke schoen.
Danielle Fournier.
Katja.
Austrian.
Italian?
Danielle Fournier, France.
Alison Hendrix,
Scarborough.
You're practically local.
And punctual.
Hello?
Hey. Did you getto the hotel?
Yeah, but somebodygot there first.
They ransacked her room.
- Shit!- No briefcase?
I didn't say that.
Did you find it, or not?
Hang on.
Screw it.
Hello?Who am I speaking to?
Beth?
Alison?
Who is this?
Who is this?!
Beth's indisposed.Is this Alison?
Just one.I'm a few.
No family, too.Who am I?
Yeah, sorry, riddler,means nothing to me.
Look, Beth said to sayI have the briefcase.
Do you want meto bring it to you?
"35 Black Oak Drive".
Stop it!
You stop it!
Hey hey hey!No no no no.
Don't hurt her.
Holy shite.
A soccer mom.
Follow your sister.Don't run.
Good boy!
Good boy.
There you go.
Over there!
Hello?
Oh.
Go. Go, go!
Vivien! I'm going tocut the... yeah.
I just want some answers.
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you show your face
in front of my children.
How did you find me?
The German had your address.
I've got what you wanted.
I've got her briefcase.
Idiot. Do you even knowwho you're talking to?
Hmm?
Where is Beth?
Uh, she's dead.
What?
I'm sorry.She killed herself.
No. No, no, shewouldn't do that.
That's impossible.
No, I'm sorry.I saw her do it.
No, that can't be.Mnh-mnh.
Look, I can explain, okay?
My name's Sarah...
I don't care who you are.
Why, Lord?Why me?
I never wantedany part of this.
Do I wear a huge"kick me" sign
on my back?
Please, just tell me...
Who are we to each other?
Are you kidding me?
I'm not doing that.
Nope, that is notmy responsibility...
You know, you needto get out of here.
Go and wait for a call.
Eh, tell me what the hell...
Let go!Don't touch me.
This is my neighborhood.
You wait for a call.
Oh, and hide your ugly face
on the way out of here.
Bitch.
Okay, oranges, guys!
Can I take two?
Yeah, you take two.
What's up, Art?
Where are you?
I'm at home in the tubwith a bourbon.
Can you hear me knocking?
No?
Because you're not home.
Okay, I'm in Scarborough.
What? Why?!
I had to go to BedBath & Beyond, okay?
Nobody wants to admit that.
Look, whatever, Beth.
What the hell did yousay to the shrink?
She's ruling youunfit for duty.
What? Why?
Yeah, unfit meansno hearing tomorrow.
Oh, shit!
It means this crap goes onand on and guess what...
I'm keeping your moneyuntil it ends.
I'll go see her now.
No no no, it's too latefor that, Beth.
Get me anotherappointment, okay?
Tell her it's an emergency,you're worried about me.
She's my doctor.She has to see me.
And what are you going to sayto her to change her mind?
I'll figure something out.
I'm sorry.
My opinion is you'renot ready for duty.
I am, though.
I'm making progress,full progress.
Go on.
You know, with the guilt,
seeing cell phoneand reacting "gun".
You're just parroting ourlast meeting back to me.
No, I'm admitting my mistake,
Dr. Bowers,
I'm acknowledging it,like you said.
Honestly, the bestthing for me now is
to get back to work.
Last time I saw you,you couldn't remember
the shooting."I'm missing myself.
I glitched.
A break,or something."
I remember it just fine.
What I'm tryingto do is move on.
Sorry, Beth, but, considering
your mental state, leadingup to the incident...
That's behind me now,Dr. Bowers.
And by your own admission ofblackout or psychotic break,
I can't recommend you for duty.
That's not going towork for me.
I understand, you're a cop,
but this is my job.
Can you read that back again?
That, um,
"I'm missing myself.I glitched."
Does that sound stoned to you?
"Glitched" sounds stoned?
Tweaked, gakked, spun.
Ahem!Allevia,
superprax, draxifil.
What's the differencebetween a mood stabilizer
and an antipsychotic, again?
Beth...
Oh, no, I'm sorry,I've been confused.
I mean, it's very confusing.
Um...
Antidepressants,antianxieties, SSRIs.
Serotronax...That one's a stimulant.
We have known each otherfor a while, now, Beth...
Yeah? That's whereyou're wrong.
You have constantlytested me
with your personal appealsfor prescriptions.
I know.
My bad.
So I'll just explainto the board
that I shot this poorcivilian after mixing up
all your overlapping scrips.
Or am I making progress?
All right, if everybody here,
let's see if wecould do this again.
The board convenes in a fatal
line-of-duty shooting,October 7th of this year.
State your name and rankfor the record
and begin.
Detective Elizabeth Childs.
You did well.
We'll have a rulingin a couple of days.
Okay.
This is Sarah.
Well, Sarah,this will be quick.
Good.
Since you apparentlyalready know where I live
and I can't find a sitter,
come by after 9:00tonight.
How about right now?
Tonight! Bring whateveryou got from the German.
Go around back and goto the basement door.
Knock quietly!
Not bad, Childs.
Not bad.
I nailed it, man,
every detail.
Yeah. They haven'truled yet.
Please contain your excitement.
This is me, excited.
Come on, Art,
give me a littlelove, here, yeah?
Why do you have to besuch a hardass?
Because
it's your favoritething about me.
Look, Paul doesn't know
I took that moneyout of our account.
So just let me put it back
before he finds out, yeah?
I hang on to it 'tilyou're reinstated.
That's the deal.
There was no deal,it was just you, taking...
Looking out for you,
partner.
Oh, my God!Ugh!
You know I neverwould've got in
if you said we weregoing to suburbia.
Oi, what are you doing?
Don't stop. Someonemight speak to us.
God!
Christ.
You know, my skinjust breaks out
every time I leavethe downtown.
Yeah, yeah.
Right there.Look... acne.
No,
I don't see acne.
Am I blushing?
There's redness!Right there!
Tiny, little suburbanstress zits, emerging
in direct proximityto bad architecture.
Look, Fe,
I'm going to have themoney in a couple days.
Okay? And then...Look,
I'll make good with Mrs. S.
and we'll take Kirasomewhere quiet, yeah?
Somewhere warm.
Yeah, please.
So what's in the house?
I won't be long.
Oh, my God!Who's in there?
Stay here, okay?
Is it the German?
The German's dead.
She's dead?!She died?!
Sadly, yes.
This one's an uptight
Soccer mom.
Hey, Sarah! You alwaysdo this to me!
I just need you to bemy backup, okay?
I don't do backup!
I don't even knowwhat backup is!
Give me half an hour.
What am I supposedto do 'til then?
Nothing.
I just need somebodyto know where I am.
Wait, that is notcomforting! Sarah!
Sh...!
Close it, lock it.
Really?
Be quiet. My kidsare sleeping.
You're going to shoot me
while your kids are sleeping?
You wake them or show yourface, yes, I will shoot you.
Well I've never knowna blood relation,
but being your twincertainly sucks.
You really haveno idea, do you?
Hey.
I'm Cosima.
Bloody hell.
We talked on the phone.
How many of us are there?
We're clones. We'resoneone's experiment
and they're killing us off!
Is that helpful?
Oh, my God! What areyou doing in my yard?
You want answers,I want the briefcase.
Seriously, life or death.
What kind of mother am I
if I snatch my own daughter?
You're reinstated.
Oh, shit!
Yes, I'm at thebloody crime scene,
pretending to be a bloody cop,
so I need to know if thebloody fingerprints
will flag a bloody match.
Freeze! Police!